Guide to the Edmund White Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- July 1991 Acquisition, Series I; 24.92; (27 boxes)
  - Writings, 1950-92
    - Writings by Edmund White
      - Notes: holograph, undated; 10 (Box 12)
      - Notes: typescript, undated (Box 12)
      - "The Oakes Family": essay, clipping, undated (Box 12)
      - "Odile Hellier at the Village Voice": article, typescript, undated (Box 12)
      - "On Becoming a Model for Male Smut": essay, typescript, undated (Box 12)
      - "On Narcissistic Atheism": essay, holograph, undated (Box 12)
      - "On Reading": article, Town and Country, 1983 May (Box 12)
      - "The Oracle": short story, Out, 1986 October-December (Box 12)
      - "The Orton Diaries": The Sunday Times, article, 1986 November 23 (Box 12)
      - "Paradise Found": Mother Jones, article, 1983 June (Box 12)
      - Paris articles: clippings, 1984-1990 (Box 12)
      - "Parnassus in Houston": The Soho News, article, 1981 January 14 (Box 12)
      - "The Passionate Friends": short story, holograph, undated (Box 12)
      - "Patrick Sarfati": Athletes, introduction, 1990 (Box 12)
      - "Peggy Guggenheim": Quest, article, 1979 May (Box 12)
      - "Périgord Pleasures": article, typescript, undated (Box 12)
      - "Personal Dispatch": Tribe 1:2, essay, 1990 Spring (Box 12)
      - "Peter and France": outline, typescript, undated (Box 12)
      - "Play for Robert Wilson": play, holograph, undated (Box 12)
      - Poems: holograph, circa 1950 (Box 12)
      - Poems and Essays: holograph, circa 1959 (Box 12)
      - "The Political Vocabulary of Homosexuality": essay, The Living Language, 1984 (Box 12)
      - "The Politics of Drag": Village Voice, article, 1979 June 25 (Box 12)
      - "Portland and Seattle": Christopher Street, article, 1979 February (Box 12)
      - "Prague: A Disappearing Poem": article typescript, corrected, undated (Box 12)
      - Private Disquisition: novel, holograph, undated (Box 12)
      - "A Quartet of Spectaculars": Horizon article, 1977 May (Box 12)
      - "The Renaissance Man": short story, typescript, undated (Box 12)
      - "Residence on Earth: Living with AIDS in the 1980s": essay, Life, 1989 Fall (Box 12)
      - Reviews
        - Kobo Abe, The Ark Sakura New York Times Book Review, 1988 April 10 (Box 12)
        - John Ashberry, Self-Portrait in a Convex Mirror, Washington Post, 1975 May 11 (Box 12)
        - James Baldwin, Just Above My Head, Washington Post, 1979 September 23 (Box 12)
        - Roland Barthes, The Empire of Signs, The New York Times Book Review, 1982 September 12 (Box 12)
        - Karl Beckson, Arthur Symons, TLS, 1987 November 13-19 (Box 12)
        - Alan P. Bell, Homosexualities, Washington Post, 1978 August 20 (Box 13)
        - L. Bergreen, James Agee: A Life, The New Republic, 1984 September 3 (Box 13)
        - Jennifer Birkett, The Sins of the Fathers, The Times, undated (Box 13)
        - Deirdra Blair, Simone de Beauvoir: A Biography, Book World, 1990 April 15 (Box 13)
        - B. Brophy, Palace Without Chairs, New York Times Book Review, 1978 July 16 (Box 13)
        - Truman Capote, A Capote Reader, TLS, 1988 May 13-19 (Box 13)
        - Bruce Chatwin, The Songlines, Sunday Times, 1987 July 5 (Box 13)
        - Robert Coover, A Night at the Movies, New York Times Book Review, 1987 February 1 (Box 13)
        - Edward Dahlberg, The Carnal Myth, The New Republic, 1968 August 3 (Box 13)
        - E. L. Doctorow, World's Fair, The Nation, 1985 November 30 (Box 13)
        - M. Foucault, The Care of the Self, Sunday Times, 1988 May 8 (Box 13)
        - M. Foucault, Herculine Barbin, The Nation, 1980 June 7 (Box 13)
        - William Gass, Habitation of the Word, Book World, 1985 March (Box 13)
        - Jean Genet, Querelle, New York Times Book Review, 1974 September 8 (Box 13)
        - William Gibson, A Mass for the Dead, New Republic, 1968 May 4 (Box 13)
        - Victoria Glendinning, Elizabeth Bowen, Washington Post, 1978 February 5 (Box 13)
        - Mary Gordon, Final Payments, Washington Post NOS, 1978 April 9 (Box 13)
        - Juan Goyisolo, Landscapes after the Battle, Book World, 1987 June 14 (Box 13)
        - David Grossman, See Under: Love, New York Times Book Review, 1989 April 16 (Box 13)
        - Elizabeth Hardwick, Sleepless Nights, Washington Post, 1979 May 6 (Box 13)
        - Christopher Isherwood, My Guru and his Disciple and Christopher and His Kind, New York Times Book Review, 1980 June 1; 2 (Box 13)
        - Derek Jarman, Caravaggio, Literary Review, 1968 May (Box 13)
        - Franz Kafka, Letters to Friends, Family, and Editors, Washington Post, 1978 January 1 (Box 13)
        - Y. Kawabata, The Lake, New York Times Book Review, 1974 June 23 (Box 13)
        - Marjoire Kellog, Tell Me That You Love Me, Junie Moon, New Republic, 1968 November 23 (Box 13)
        - Maxine Hong Kingston, China Men, Book World, 1980 June 22 (Box 13)
        - Peter Klappert, The Idiot Princess of the Last Dynasty, The New Republic, 1985 October 28 (Box 13)
        - Billy Klüver, Kiki's Paris, New York Times Book Review, 1989 June 11 (Box 13)
        - David Leavitt, Equal Affections, Literary Review, 1989 May (Box 13)
        - Fran Lebowitz, Metropolitan Life, Washington Post, 1978 April 30 (Box 13)
        - G. Leopardi, The Moral Essays, New York Times Book Review, 1983 June 19 (Box 13)
        - José Lezama Lima, Paradiso, New York Times Book Review, 1974 April 2 (Box 13)
        - Charles Lockwood, Suddenly San Francisco, Washington Post, 1978 July 21 (Box 13)
        - Alison Lurie, The Truth about Lorin Jones, New York Times Book Review, 1988 September 4 (Box 13)
        - Lachlan MacKinnon, Monterey Cyprus and Alan Jenkins, In the Hothouse, The Sunday Times, 1988 May 29 (Box 13)
        - Thomas McMahon, McKay's Bees, New York Times Book Review, 1979 August 19 (Box 13)
        - Frank MacShane, Into Eternity, The York Times Book Review, 1985 December 9 (Box 13)
        - André Malraux, Anti-Memories, Newsweek, 1968 October 21 (Box 13)
        - William Maxwell, So Long, See You Tomorrow, Washington Post, 1980 January 13 (Box 13)
        - Patrick Merla, Tales, Washington Post, 1985 September 22 (Box 13)
        - Y. Mishima, Runaway Horses, New York Times Book Review, 1973 June 24 (Box 13)
        - Elsa Morante, History, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 13)
        - Ted Morgan, Maugham, Chicago Sun- Times, 1980 March 30 (Box 13)
        - Ivan Morris, The Nobility of Failure, Washington Post, 1975 August 29 (Box 13)
        - Vladimir Nabokov, The Enchanter, New York Times Book Review, 1986 October 26 (Box 13)
        - Newsweek, Saturday Review, 1968-1973 (Box 13)
        - P. Pasolini, Poems, New York Times Book Review, 1982 June 27 (Box 13)
        - Joseph Pearce, Magical Child, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 13)
        - Ishmael Reed, Flight to Canada, The Nation, 1976 September 18 (Box 13)
        - Gerhard Roth, Winterreise, Book World, 1980 November 23 (Box 13)
        - A. E. Rowse, The Poet Auden, Literary Review, 1987 May (Box 13)
        - Edward Said, Orientalism, Washington Post, 1978 December (Box 13)
        - Maria St. Just, Five O'Clock Angel, New York Times Book Review, 1990 May 27 (Box 13)
        - The Simon Weil Reader, Washington Post, 1977 October 2 (Box 13)
        - Isaac Bashevis Singer, The Séance and Other Stories, The New Republic, undated (Box 13)
        - W. M. Spackman, A Presence with Secrets, Village Voice, 1981 January 14-20 (Box 13)
        - Muriel Spark, Territorial Rights, New York Times Book Review, 1979 May 20 (Box 13)
        - Donald Spoto, The Kindness of Strangers, The New Republic, 1985 May 13 (Box 13)
        - Christina Stead, Ocean of Story, New York Times Book Review, 1986 May 25 (Box 13)
        - Junichiro Tanizaki, Naomi, The New Republic, 1985 November 15 (Box 13)
        - J[unichiro] Tanizaki, Secret History of the Lord of Musashi, New York Times Book Review, 1982 July 18 (Box 13)
        - John Updike, Marry Me: A Romance, Washington Post, undated (Box 13)
        - Gore Vidal, Essays 1973-76, Harper's, 1977 May (Box 13)
        - M. E. White, In the Balance, New Republic, 1968 February 24 (Box 13)
        - Tennesse Williams, Collected Stories, The Sunday Times, 1986 October 5 (Box 13)
        - Robert Wilson, Einstein on the Beach, Christopher Street, 1977 January (Box 13)
        - Jeanette Winterson, The Passion, The Sunday Times, 1987 Junu 21 (Box 13)
      - "A Reveiw of Man Makes Himself and the Science of Culture", essay, typescript, undated (Box 13)
      - "Richard Ford": article, holograph, undated (Box 13)
      - Rimbaud: play
        - Typescript, photocopy, undated; 2 (Box 13)
        - Copyright, 1963 February 19 (Box 13)
      - "Roland Barthes": notes, holograph, undated (Box 13)
      - "Ronald Firbank" (incomplete), The Advocate, article, 1975 November 5 (Box 13)
      - "Running on Empty": short story
        - Holograph, undated (Box 13)
        - Typescript, undated (Box 13)
      - "Russian Reverie": article, House and Garden, 1990 Jan (Box 13)
      - "A Sacred Satire": short story, corrected galleys, photocopy, 1989 (Box 13)
      - "Sado Machismo": New York Times, 1979 January 8 (Box 13)
      - "Safe Sex Fantasy": short story, typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 13)
      - "The Saintliness of Christopher Isherwood", Literary Review, 1986 May (Box 13)
      - "Santa Fe, Salt Lake City, and Denver": Christopher Street, essay, 1979 April (Box 13)
      - "Sartre Would Have Loved Her": article Sunday Times Magazine, 1987 October 11 (Box 13)
      - "The Secret Order of Joy": short story, Paris Review, 1982 Summer (Box 13)
      - The Seduction: one-act play, typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 13)
      - "Sex and Language": article, Soho News, 1981 May 6-12 (Box 14)
      - Sex Secrets of the World: book, typescript, undated (Box 14)
      - "Short story about my aunt": short story holograph, undated (Box 14)
      - 666: play
        - Notes: holograph, undated (Box 14)
        - Typescript, undated (Box 14)
      - "Skinned Alive": short story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 14)
      - "A Sled on the Steppes": short story, typescript, undated (Box 14)
      - "Slip of the Salad Oil": short story, holograph (unfinished), undated (Box 14)
      - The Snow Queen, the Crystal With and the Prince of Puerto Rico: play, typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 14)
      - Something Valentine: novel
        - Notes: holograph, undated (Box 14)
        - Holograph, Part 1, first draft, undated (Box 14)
        - Holograph, Part 2, first draft, undated (Box 14)
        - Holograph, Part 3, first draft, undated (Box 14)
        - Typescript, carbon [5 copies ], undated; 6 (Box 14)
      - "South Bank Show Opening Remarks": lecture, typescript, undated (Box 14)
      - "A Spanish Nocturne": short story
        - Typescript, carbon, undated (Box 14)
        - Chicago Review 30:1, 1978 Summer (Box 14)
      - "Speculative Fictions": essay, typescript, carbon, holograph, undated (Box 14)
      - "Stage Door": musical
        - Holograph, typescript, 1978 July (Box 14)
        - Typescript, 1978 (Box 14)
      - "Stanislavski in Pekonio": short story, typescript, undated (Box 14)
      - "Statement at Age 37", lecture, typescript, photocopy, 1977 (Box 14)
      - States of Desire: book
        - Proposal, typescript, 1978 March 29 (Box 14)
        - Contract, 1978 May 2 (Box 14)
        - Notes, holograph, undated; 2 (Box 14)
        - Notes, holograph, undated; 3 (Box 15)
        - Maps, undated (Box 15)
        - Research files, 1978-1979; 6 (Box 15)
        - Expenses, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
        - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 15)
        - Atlanta: Brown's Guide, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
        - Atlanta: Cruise, 1978 October (Box 15)
        - Atlanta: miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 15)
        - "Boston and Washington, D.C.", holograph, undated (Box 15)
        - "Boston and Washington, D.C.", typescript, carbon, undated (Box 15)
        - California, Gay Life, 1978 June (Box 15)
        - Chicago, 1979 January (Box 15)
        - Flordia: The Advocate, 1979 June 14 (Box 15)
        - Florida: Alive, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
        - Florida: This Week with David, 1978 December 8-14 (Box 15)
        - "Florida and the South," notes, holograph, undated (Box 15)
        - "Florida and the South": typescript, undated (Box 15)
        - "Florida and the South": typescript, carbon, undated (Box 15)
        - Kansas City Visitor, 1978 (Box 15)
        - Los Angeles: research files, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
        - "Los Angeles": holograph, undated (Box 15)
        - "Los Angeles": typescript, carbon, undated (Box 15)
        - The Midwest: Gay Life, 1978 July 28 (Box 15)
        - The Midwest: miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 15)
        - The Midwest: holograph, undated (Box 16)
        - "The Midwest: Cities of the Plain": typescript, carbon, undated (Box 16)
        - Minneapolis: research files, 1973, 1978 (Box 16)
        - New England: Esplanade, 1979 June 20 (Box 16)
        - New Orleans: Figaro, 1979 February 19 (Box 16)
        - New Orleans: Impact, 1979 (Box 16)
        - "New York": holograph, undated (Box 16)
        - "New York": typescript, carbon, undated (Box 16)
        - Portland, Oregon: directory, 1978 (Box 16)
        - "Portland and Seattle": holograph, undated (Box 16)
        - "Portland and Seattle": typescript, carbon, undated (Box 16)
        - Salt Lake City: Mormonism research file, 1977-1978 (Box 16)
        - Salt Lake City: The Open Door, 1978 October-December; 3 (Box 16)
        - San Francisco: Gay Freedom Day Program, 1978 January 18-25 (Box 16)
        - San Francisco: miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 16)
        - "San Francisco": holograph, undated (Box 16)
        - "San Francisco": typescript, undated (Box 16)
        - "Santa Fe, Salt Lake City and Denver:" holograph, undated (Box 16)
        - Seattle Gay News, 1978 October 13 (Box 16)
        - Seattle Sun, 1978 June 21 (Box 16)
        - Seattle Times, 1978 June 24 (Box 16)
        - Seattle: miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 16)
        - Texas: research files, 1977-1978 (Box 16)
        - "Texas": holograph, undated (Box 16)
        - "Texas": typescript, carbon, undated (Box 16)
        - Washington, D.C.: The Georgetowner, 1978 February 9-22 (Box 16)
        - Washington, D.C.: The Washington Guidebook, 1969 (Box 16)
        - Washington, D.C.: research files, 1978-1979 (Box 16)
        - "Washington, D.C.": holograph, undated (Box 16)
        - "Epilogue: Self-Criticism": typescript, carbon, undated (Box 16)
        - Report of copy-editor, typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 16)
        - British contract, 1980 March 11 (Box 16)
        - Royalties, 1980-1981 (Box 16)
        - Reviews, 1980; 7 (Box 16)
        - British reviews, 1980-1981; 4 (Box 16)
      - "Stavisky": article, Soho Weekly News, 1974 October 3 (Box 17)
      - "Straight Woman, Gay Men": article, typescript, photocopy, 1989 February 28 (Box 17)
      - "Stravinsky and His Music": Great Men of Music, article, 1975 (Box 17)
      - "Strong Stuff: Ewa Kuryluk": Art in General, article, 1984 March-April (Box 17)
      - "Le Style Jacques Grange": House and Garden, article, 1989 July (Box 17)
      - "Surreal Note in Belgium": Architectural Digest, article, 1989 December (Box 17)
      - "Susan Sontag": lecture notes, holograph, 1983 (Box 17)
      - "Sweating Mirrors: Interview with Capote": After Dark, article, 1980 September (Box 17)
      - "The Swimming-Pool Library": article, holograph, undated (Box 17)
      - "Tangier-A Biographer's Quest": article second draft, typescript, undated (Box 17)
      - "Tangier Odyssey: Jean Genet": article, Vogue, 1988 December (Box 17)
      - "Tanizaki": article, holograph, undated (Box 17)
      - The Tarantulas: television script, typescript, undated (Box 17)
      - "Testimony": essay, City Lights Review, 1988 (Box 17)
      - "Their Masks, Their Lives": essay, typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 17)
      - "Their Masks, Their Lives: Harry Mathews' Cigarettes: essay, Review of Contemporary Fiction, 1987 Fall (Box 17)
      - "This is not a Mammal: A Visit With William Burroughs": article, Soho News, 1981 February 18-21 (Box 17)
      - Three Friends: novel
        - Notes, holograph, undated (Box 17)
        - Holograph, typescript, undated (Box 17)
        - Holograph, undated (Box 17)
        - Typescript, undated; 2 (Box 17)
        - Typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 17)
      - Three Times Three: play
        - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 17)
        - Typescript, photocopy, undated; 3 (Box 17)
      - Three-twelve Bluebird: play
        - Typescript, undated; 2 (Box 18)
        - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 18)
      - The Tower Window: novel, typescript, undated (Box 18)
      - "Travel: Turkey": article, Vogue, 1986 May (Box 18)
      - Trios ( Three Times Three ): reviews, 1990 (Box 18)
      - "A Trip Up North": short story, typescript, undated (Box 18)
      - Two-part Inventions: play
        - Typescript, undated; 2 (Box 18)
        - Memorabilia, undated (Box 18)
        - Copyright, 1965 January 13 (Box 18)
      - "Two Vignettes", typescript, undated (Box 18)
      - "The Urban Strategist": New York, article, undated (Box 18)
      - "The Usual Talk": short story, typescript, undated (Box 18)
      - "Venice Through the Looking Glass": article, Departures, 1987 May (Box 18)
      - "Violets for her Furs": short story, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 18)
      - Vogue: article, clippings, 1984 (Box 18)
      - Washington Post: reviews, clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 18)
      - "What Makes Dance Our Most Vital Art Form?": article, New York Times, 1975 June 1 (Box 18)
      - "The Wild Duck": essay, holograph, undated (Box 18)
      - "William Burroughs": article, holograph, undated (Box 18)
      - "William McPherson": article, holograph, undated (Box 18)
      - Woman Reading Pascal: novel
        - Holograph, undated (Box 18)
        - Typescript, undated; 3 (Box 18)
        - Rejected pages, holograph, undated (Box 18)
        - Rejected pages, typescript, undated (Box 18)
      - A Woman's Place: play
        - Typescript, [1970?] (Box 18)
        - Typescript, carbon, 1970 (Box 18)
      - "Zone Therapy": play, holograph, undated (Box 18)
      - "Zurich: The Art of Happiness": article, typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 18)
      - Unidentified article: holograph, [1989?] (Box 18)
      - Unidentified play: holograph, undated (Box 18)
      - Unidentified play: holograph, undated (Box 18)
      - Unidentified short story: typescript, undated (Box 18)
      - Unidentified short story: typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 18)
      - Unidentified, undated; 16 (Box 19)
    - Writings of Others
      - Agamben, Giorgio, "Sui limiti della violenza": essay, offprint, undated (Box 19)
      - Bergman, David, "Alternative Service: Families in Recent Gay Fiction": essay, photocopy, 1986 (Box 19)
      - Bockman, Philip, Untitled novel, photocopy, undated (Box 19)
      - Bompiani, Gineura, "Le specie del sonno": essay, offprint, undated (Box 19)
      - Corn, Alfred
        - "The Column": poem, offprint, 1980 (Box 19)
        - "Solos": novel, typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 19)
      - Dlugos, Tim, Je Suis Ein Americano: poetry, typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 19)
      - Dowell, Coleman, "The Snake's House": short story, typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 19)
      - Dureau, George, Exhibition catalogue, 1977 (Box 19)
      - Finlayson, Iain, "Tangier": article, typescript, 1988 August (Box 19)
      - Fleming, Keith
        - "Life in the New World": short story, Chicago Literary World, 1981 Spring (Box 19)
        - "W. M. Spackman": article, Chicago Literary Review, 1981 March 13 (Box 19)
      - George-Murray, Richard, Lilac Cure: poems, offprint, 1976 November (Box 19)
      - Glass, Laurence d' A. M., Selected Prose Poems and Verse, typescript, photocopy, 1980 (Box 19)
      - Hellesto, Mark, "Interview with Edmund White": typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 19)
      - Kundera, Milan (translated by Edmund White), "The Tragedy of Central Europe": The New York Review of Books, article, 1984 April 26 (Box 19)
      - Merla, Patrick, Seven Fairy Tales: stories, typescript, photocopy, 1976 (Box 19)
      - Mitzel, John, "The Boston Sex Scandel": article, photocopy, 1979 (Box 19)
      - Moloney, James, "The Emotional Convictions of the Analyst": article, offprint, 1957 (Box 19)
      - Prologue: An examination of the Mormon attitude toward homosexuality: booklet, 1977 (Box 19)
      - White, Delilah, "IQ Changes in Mongoloid Children during Post-Maturation Treatment": offprint, 1969 March (Box 19)
      - White, E. V., Folks are Funny: photocopy, 1937 (Box 19)
      - Whitmore, George
        - "The Moon and the Sun on Fire Island": short story, typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 19)
        - Photo Real: play, typescript, photocopy, undated (Box 19)
        - Three Poems for "Cripple Creek ", typescript, photocopy, 1976 (Box 19)
        - "To Edmund, a Poem Not in my Style": holograph, 1974 (Box 19)
        - Tricking: mimeograph, 1974 (Box 19)
        - "That Time of Month": short stories, typescript, photocopy, 1980 July-August (Box 19)
      - Woodard, Luke
        - Sketches of a Life at 75: photocopy, undated (Box 19)
        - Woodard family memoirs, undated (Box 19)
      - Unidentified, undated; 5 (Box 19)
  - Financial Papers, 1964-1988
    Series III, Financial Papers, is arranged chronologically.
    - Passbook, 1964-1965 (Box 20)
    - Daybooks, 1970 (Box 20)
    - Daybook, 1970 (Box 20)
    - Income tax return, 1971 (Box 20)
    - Cancelled checks, 1971; 2 (Box 20)
    - Income tax return, 1972 (Box 20)
    - Daybook, 1972 (Box 20)
    - Bills and receipts, 1972 (Box 20)
    - Checkbooks, 1972-1973; 2 (Box 20)
    - Cancelled checks, 1972-1973 (Box 20)
    - Aninger, Peter, bills and receipts, 1972-1973; 4 (Box 20)
    - Ingram Merrill Foundation, 1973 (Box 20)
    - Contracts, 1973 (Box 20)
    - American Express: bills and receipts, 1974 (Box 20)
    - Manufacturers Hanover Trust Co.: statement and passbook, 1974 (Box 20)
    - Bills and receipts, 1974 (Box 20)
    - Payments and receipts, 1974; 2 (Box 20)
    - Cancelled checks, 1974; 2 (Box 20)
    - Checkbooks, 1974; 2 (Box 20)
    - Daybook, 1974 (Box 20)
    - Income tax return, 1974 (Box 20)
    - Cancelled checks, 1975; 2 (Box 20)
    - Checkbooks, 1975; 2 (Box 21)
    - Bills and receipts, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Air Tickets stubs, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Income tax return and estimates, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Credit card receipts, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Daybook, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Income tax return, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Daybook, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Bills and receipts, 1976; 2 (Box 21)
    - Contracts and payments, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Cancelled checks, 1976; 2 (Box 21)
    - Checkbooks, 1976; 3 (Box 21)
    - Tax return, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Contracts and payments, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Life insurance policies, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Bills and receipts, 1977; 4 (Box 21)
    - Cancelled checks, 1977; 2 (Box 21)
    - Daybook, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Checkbooks, 1977; 3 (Box 21)
    - Tax return, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Financial papers, 1978 (Box 22)
    - Tax return, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Checks and payments, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Phone and utilities bills, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Credit card receipts, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Bank statements, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Air tickets, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Checkbooks, 1979-1981; 2 (Box 22)
    - Income tax return, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Credit card receipts, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Cancelled checks, 1980; 2 (Box 22)
    - Contracts and payments, 1980 (Box 22)
    - Receipts, 1980-1981 (Box 22)
    - Income tax return, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Contracts and payments, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Bills and receipts, 1981 (Box 22)
    - Bank statements, 1981-1982 (Box 22)